Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
- Johnson, Stephen P., 1977 (Box 43, Folder 43)
- Palm, Charles E., 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 44)
- Planning and Facilities, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 45)
- Chairmen Responses, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Biological Sciences (O'Brien, R. D.), 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Biochemistry, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 48)
- Ecology, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 49)
- Neurobiology, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 50)
- Wiegand Herbarium, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 51)
- Agricultural Economics, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 52-53)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 54)
- Agronomy, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 55)
- Atmospheric Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 56)
- Animal Science, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 57-58)
- Animal Science Farm, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 59)
- Dairy Days, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 60)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 61)
- Communication Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 62)
- Communication Arts Search Committee, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 63)
- Colle, Royal D., 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 64-65)
- Media Services, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 66)
- White, Shirley--Proposal, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 67)
- Education, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 68)
- Education Chairmanship, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 69)
- Institute of Occupational Education, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 70)
- Entomology, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 71-72)
- Pimentel, David--Pesticide News Releases, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 73-74)
- Cooperative Extension, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
- County Agents, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- 4-H, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Finance and Business Office, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Floriculture, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Landscape Architecture, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Food Science, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Pesticide Lab, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Microbiology, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Microbiology Search Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Buck, Paul, 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 12-13)
- Geneva, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 14-15)
- Barton, D. W.--Construction Program, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Geneva--Entomology Headship, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Tree Fruit Pest Management Project, Proposal, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Barton, Donald W., 1978 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Splittstoesser Committee, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- International Agriculture Development (IAD), 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 21-22)
- IAD Newsletters, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Mann Library, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Natural Resources, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 25-26)
- Shackelton Point, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Plant Breeding, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Biometry, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Plant Pathology, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Pomology--Ithaca and Geneva, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Poultry, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Potential Increases in Food Supply Through Research in Agriculture (VanDemark, N. L.--Chairman), 1976 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Resident Instruction, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 34-36)
- Minority Program for College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Placement, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Research, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 39-40)
- New Professors, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 41)
- Rural Sociology, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 42)
- Vegetable Crops, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Lab, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 44)
- Long Island Dedication, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 45)
- Correspondence--A, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Academic Funding, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 47)
- Accessory Instruction, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 48)
- Admissions and Financial Aid, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 49)
- Africana Studies and Research Center, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 50)
- AgFAX, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 51)
- Ag PAC, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 52)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 53)
- Council of Agricultural Organizations, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 54)
- Agricultural Resources Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 55)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 56-57)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 58)
- United States Secretary of Agriculture, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 59)
- Agway, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 60)
- Alpha Zeta, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 61)
- Alumni Association, Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 62)
- Alumni Office, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 63)
- American Agriculturist, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 64)
- Aquaculture, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 65)
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 66)
- Athletic Department, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 67)
- Correspondence--B, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 68)
- Best Management Practices for Agriculture and Silviculture, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 69)
- Brady, Nyle C., 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 70)
- Correspondence--C, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 71)
- Council for Agricultural Science and Technology (CAST), 1978 (Box 44, Folder 72)
- Cohn Farm, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 73)
- Commissioner of Commerce, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Computer Activity Group, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Convocation, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Cornell Plantations, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc., 1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Correspondence--D, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Dairy Forage Research, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
- Dairy Management, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- University Development, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Dog Tick, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Correspondence--E, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- New York State Department of Education, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Education, Postsecondary, Temporary Commission on SUNY Trustees Statement to, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Empire Farm Days, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Empire State Soil Fertility, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Energy, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- College of Engineering, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Enrollments, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Environmental Protection Agency, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Center for Environmental Research (CER), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- CER Charter, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- College of Environmental Sciences and Forestry, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 25-26)
- Exxon, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Correspondence--F, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Facilities Inventory, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Faculty with Cornell Degrees, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- FMC Corporation, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Food Policy Workshop, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Correspondence--G, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Geneva Computer, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Golden Nematode, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Graduate School, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Board of Trustees, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Chancellor (Corson, D. R.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Counsel (Bugliari, J. B.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Dean of the Faculty (Saunders, Byron), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 40)
- Assistant to the President (Barlow, J. R.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 41)
- President (Rhodes, Frank H. T.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 42)
- Provost (Knapp, D. C.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 43)
- Real Estate, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 44)
- Vice Provost (Barlow, Mark), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 45)
- Senior Vice President (Herbster, W. G.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 46)
- Vice President for Administration (Lawrence, S. A.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 47)
- Vice President and Chief Investment Office (Horn), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 48)
- Vice President for Land-Grant Affairs (Cook, C. E.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 49-50)
- Vice President for Planning (Matyas, R. M.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 51)
- Vice President for Public Affairs (Ramin, R. M.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 52)
- Vice President for Research (Cooke, W. D.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 53)
- Department Chairmens' Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 54)
- SUNY--Academic Programs (Van Arnam, Kathryn), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 55)
- SUNY--Alumni Association, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 56)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 57)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Kelly, James F.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 58)
- SUNY--Chancellor's Forum, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 59)
- SUNY--Associate Chancellor for Public Service (Ingler, Charles W.), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 60)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 61-63)
- SUNY--Deputy Commissioner (Spencer, Robert), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 64)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 65)
- SUNY--Graduate Council, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 66)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 67)
- SUNY--Provost (Baritz, Loren), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 68)
- SUNY--Provost (Gordon, Sanford), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 69)
- SUNY--Provost for Academic Programs (Neff, Charles), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 70)
- SUNY--Provost for Research (Silverman), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 71)
- SUNY--Provost for University Planning (MacKenzie, Kenneth), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 72)
- SUNY--Reduction in Staff, State Policy, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 73)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Campus Development (Lanford, Oscar), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 74)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Educational Services (Smoot, James S.), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 75)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations (Komisar, Jerome), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 76)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Finance and Business (Spindler, Harry), 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 77)
- SUNY--Women, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 78)
- SUNY--Community Colleges, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 79)
- SUNY--Agricultural and Technical Colleges, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 80)
- SUNY--Agricultural and Technical Colleges, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 81)
- Correspondence--H, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 82)
- Housing, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 83)
- How Much Support Should New York State Provide for Agricultural Research?, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 84)
- School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 85)
- Inauguration of Rhodes, Frank, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 86)
- Information, College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 87)
- Institutional Planning and Analysis, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 88)
- Center of International Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 89-90)
- Inventory of Relationships with Agricultural Industries and Other Constituencies, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 91)
- Isles of Shoals, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 92)
- Correspondence--J, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 93)
- Correspondence--K, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 94)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 95)
- Kennedy, Laing, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 96)
- King, Joe, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 97)
- Correspondence--L, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 98)
- Law School, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 99)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 100)
- Members of Assembly, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 101)
- Assembly Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Assembly Intern Program, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Members of Congress, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Office of Management and Budget (Washington, D.C.), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Senators, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Wampler Bill, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
- Correspondence--M, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Campus Master Plan, 1972-1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Milk, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Miner Institute, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 11-12)
- Agriculture in Northern New York, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Correspondence--N, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- New York Hereford Association, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- New York Soil Conservation Districts Association, Inc., 1977 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- New York State Food Industry Development Center, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Meeting With Non-Tenured Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Correspondence--O, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Onion Research Order, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Ornithology Lab, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Correspondence--P, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Performance Appraisal, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Personnel, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Pine Mice, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Professors-At-Large, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Correspondence--R, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- RCA Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 32-33)
- Reception for President Rhodes, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Office of Registrar, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Rehabilitation Act Material, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 36)
- Research--Agriculture by Private Industry, Survey, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Retiring Faculty, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Rural Development--Wyoming County, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Council on Rural Education, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- Sea Grant, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 41-42)
- Service and Analysis of Trends, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- Sludge, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 44)
- Soil Conservation Service, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 45)
- Soil and Water Management Programs, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 46)
- Science, Technology, and Society (STS), 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 47)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 48)
- Correspondence--T, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 49)
- Teaching Assistants, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 50)
- Proposal to Taiwan Government, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 51)
- Title V--Rural Development, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 52)
- Title XII, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 53-54)
- Traffic Bureau, 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 55)
- Transfer Students, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 56)
- Correspondence--U, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 57)
- Uihlein Farm, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 58)
- Uihlein Ground Breaking Ceremony, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 59)
- University Council, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 60)
- Urban Gardens, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 61)
- Correspondence--S, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 62)
- USDA, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 63)
- United States Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Lab, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--V, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 65)
- Veterinary College, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 66)
- Correspondence--W, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 67)
- Young President's Association (YPO), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 68)
- Correspondence--XYZ, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 69)
- Council, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 70)
- Advisory Council, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 71)
- Advisory Council--Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 72)
- Council Membership--Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 73)
- Council Meetings, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 74)
- Council for New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 75)
- Agricultural Council, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 76)
- Council Meeting, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 77)
- Council for New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Council Membership, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Council Mailings, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Agricultural Council, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Council Mailing, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Council Spring Meeting, Geneva, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Agricultural Council Mailing, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Council Meeting, Newburgh, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Agricultural College Council, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
- Council Mailing, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Material Distributed at Council Meeting, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Agriculture College Council, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Council Membership, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Council, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Advisory Council--New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Advisory Council, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 17-18)
- Advisory Council, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Membership Advisory Council, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 20-21)
- Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 22-23)
- Advisory Council, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 24-25)
- Membership Advisory Council, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- University Budget Hearing--Geneva, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Seventy-Fifth Birthday of Agriculture and Life Sciences College, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 28-38)